Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I aspired to reach
the pinnacle of wrestling.
But I couldn't make it.
However. I hope my child will one day
represent our country in wrestling.
If I'm married to you.
it won't happen.
You may leave.
Why are you doubting your ability?
It's not like you're
too old to achieve it.
I will help you achieve it.
Are you serious?
I swear on our unborn child.
RAILWAY QUARTERS
Hey. the water tanker has arrived!
Hurry up!
Hey! Everyone. be patient
and fill your pots.
It's been four days since the metro
pipe broke. and it's still not fixed.
Damn you!
Filling one pot alone
feels like a huge task.
And someone's here with so many pots!
Who the hell are you?
Take it easy. buddy.
- Sister. make way.
- Take it easy. buddy.
Step aside. sister.
Auntie. step aside.
Will life stop
While it's racing ahead?
Hey. don't shove me!
Sister. I'm getting late.
Hey. help her get up.
Come on. fill up your pots.
Problems chase us every day
Will they ever let go?
Take it easy. buddy.
Who created this divide
Between men's and women's work. dear?
He who understands
The woman he loves lives like a King.
Take it easy. buddy.
Don't take it too hard. buddy.
Mathi!
Sweetie. wake up.
It's getting late for school.
Come on. wake up.
It's getting late.
- Please give me two minutes. Pa.
- Your two minutes are very long.
- Come on. wake up.
- I'm still sleepy. Pa.
No more excuses. Wake up!
Be a sweetheart.
Love has no barriers.
Duty seeks no reward.
A smile turns
Everything into joy.
To a hopeful heart.
Even stones seem like sugar.
Dad. don't forget to buy an eraser
on our way to school.
How many erasers would you lose?
It's not like an eraser is a big item.
It's a tiny item.
It's bound to get lost.
Fine. I'll buy you one.
Dad. lock up quick.
Let's leave.
Did your husband leave for work?
- He...
- No! Why do you ask?
Nothing. I just asked.
With so many houses around.
why do you specifically
ask my wife about it?
Why shouldn't I suspect you?
Sir. why would you ask such a thing?
Isn't it normal to ask someone
whether you've left for work?
You're making a big deal about it.
A man who is a house husband…
Goes to a newlywed woman.
and inquiring if the husband is home
or at work isn't normal.
In my case. I'm a TTR on the train. and
it takes me 3 days to get home from work.
During these three days.
my heart keeps beating fast.
- Damn. he left!
- Mani. did you switch on the motor?
I just switched on the motor.
- Hey. watchman. come over here.
- Sir!
- I'm assigning you a task.
- Sir.
- Watch the CCTV 24 hours carefully.
- Okay. Sir.
If someone is entering another flat
besides their own…
Inform me.
Sir. why are you beating around the bush?
It's my duty to catch him
and your wife red-handed.
Don't worry about it and head to work.
I'll handle it.
What?
You'll catch them red-handed. you say?
Come on. hurry up!
Once again. you're late to school.
This is not right. sweetie.
What's not right?
You woke up a child from deep sleep.
It's better for a child
to arrive late than
to be forced
to arrive at school too early.
If you keep talking like this you'll
get beatings from your Teacher.
Hurry up!
Madam!
- Bye. bye.
- Bye. I'll see you in the evening.
Where are you leaving?
We have a Parents-Teacher meeting today.
No. teacher.
today I have a wrestling match to go to.
I'm already running late.
I'll finish it and come back.
I can't wait for you.
Now that you're here.
attend the meeting. and you may leave.
So. tell me. teacher.
What do I even say?
See for yourself.
She failed in all the subjects.
She can't even finish a rhyme.
Her homework is always incomplete.
Do you make any effort
to help her study at home?
to help her study at school?
Do you even realize what you're saying?
No matter how much effort we put in.
it never seems enough to survive
in today's highly competitive world.
Okay. Teacher. What else?
What else?
She's very talkative!
She's always yapping during the class.
She's becoming a bad influence
on the other students.
Last week I checked my blood pressure.
- It's beyond 200 now.
- Oh. no!
I truly can't take this anymore.
Didn't you mention the same
during the last PTA meeting?
I don't see anything new.
Should I sign here?
- Here. go sign it!
- Thank you. Teacher.
I have a wrestling match to go to.
So I cut the line.
Sorry. sorry. I'm leaving.
Bye! Everyone. bye.
- Bye!
Is he a wrestler?
Don't be fooled!
Even a wrestler won't mention
about a match so many times.
He's not a wrestler. but his wife is.
Keerthi! Keerthi!
Come on. start!
Fierce wrestling.
Come on. Keerthi. Come on. Keerthi.
Come on. Come on.
Defend!
Coach!
Hold her down. Lock! Lock!
Hey. flip her! Flip her!
Come on. flip her.
Did you see that move?
Come on!
Fierce wrestling.
Come on. Keerthi! Come on!
Hold her down!
Come on. come on! Break the lock.
Fierce.
Wrestling.
Yayy! Hey! Hey!
Fierce.
Wrestling.
Fierce wrestling.
I thought you'd lose
when she locked you in.
Thank goodness you broke her hold
and attacked her.
What did they say during the PTA meeting?
Nothing much to say. though.
They said she's a good girl.
She's studying well.
Also. she's the teacher's pet.
Phew!
- She's her mother's daughter.
- Of course!
Congratulations. Keerthi!
- Well played!
- Thank you. Coach.
Veera. why are you carrying
so many bottles?
This is ABC juice.
And this is mixed-nut juice.
exclusively prepared by me.
And this is millet flour porridge
for lunch.
If a wife has a husband like him.
she'll be unstoppable.
You're really gifted. Keerthi.
- Bye.
- Okay. Coach.
- Who is it?
- My aunt from hometown.
- Hi. auntie. how are you?
- I'm doing well. Veera!
How are Keerthi and Mathi?
No complaints. they're doing very well.
Coming Sunday. Subbaraj's son
is getting married at the temple.
As it's our relative's wedding…
Your uncle invited you
and your family to attend it.
Why didn't he call himself?
You know your uncle very well.
You must attend the wedding.
Okay. auntie!
What was the call about?
There's a wedding happening
in the hometown. thus the invitation.
Fine. I'm leaving. I'm running late.
People in society
will be waiting for me.
Hey. what song are you playing today?
So soon. it reached 50.000 likes.
Forget about the likes.
Did you read the comments?
There's one comment…
"They may be old.
but these aunties look ravishing."
"I must kidnap them all
and take them to Andaman Island."
That's nothing.
I read another comment.
"Who's that beauty
in a black saree in the front?"
"Her husband must be a lucky fellow."
Who was in black saree?
Who else do you think?
It's Partha's wife.
Reels like this ruin many families.
Veera is the root cause of this problem.
He's doing weird things
in the name of exercise and aerobics.
He does not stop with just exercise.
How to make onion sambhar.
How to knead flour for chapatis.
He teaches it all.
I can even make peace with these things.
The other day I was returning from work…
Do you know what he was teaching my wife?
What is that "stone. paper. scissors"
you play with your daughter?
It's an easy game.
This is stone.
This is paper.
And this is scissor.
Stone. paper. scissors.
Shall we play?
What are you guys doing?
I'm paper. and he's scissors.
He's scissoring me.
Scissoring?
If we want these problems to end.
- we need to persuade him to start working.
- I agree!
That's why I spent 5.000 rupees
to throw this party.
I understand.
He's living happily with his wife.
I won't spare him. Wait and watch.
I have lot of work in the morning.
I have to go to bed early...
Oh. my!
Here I come.
What happened. Dad?
Nothing. dear.
Mom dropped the glass.
It's become a habit now.
You go back to sleep.
How many times should I tell you?
Not to sneak up on me
and kiss me on my neck.
I like it.
Dad. please don't sing.
Okay. okay. I won't sing.
Shall I tell you a story?
I don't want to hear a story.
But I want a younger brother. though.
Younger brother. you say?
Ask Mom! Ask Mom!
- Mom!
- You're not getting a younger brother.
- Shut up and sleep.
- Why not?
My classmates Deepak. Darshan. Diya.
and others have a younger brother.
I want a brother too.
That too. I want it tomorrow.
It's not a product you can get overnight
delivery on from Amazon or Flipkart.
Go back to sleep!
It doesn't happen overnight. dear.
It will take Pathu Maasam.
- What do you mean by Pathu Maasam?
- It means 10 months.
Promise?
I don't want to promise. dear.
But I will do my best to make it work.
Please sleep.
Sleep. Sleep.
If you want a younger brother.
You sleep...
What now?
What about her wish?
So. I'm here.
Fine. come with me.
Rightfully. I should've been a
National champion. but I'm not.
The reason I'm not
is because I got married to you.
And had her.
If we plan for another child…
I should forget about wrestling for good
and stay at home.
Mary Kom had three children.
yet she won championships.
Why can't you do it as well?
I'm no Mary Kom. Spare me...
Hey. where's your gaze
Wandering off to?
Yeah… so what?
Chemistry is inevitable
Sparks are bound to fly.
We'll find out soon enough.
A beauty so divine
Would be a sin to leave it unnoticed.
Don't make me beg. my love.
I'm no saint
Your touch ruins my sleep.
Keep your distance. darling.
You're dangerously irresistible.
Get lost Go cool off!
You're a wild storm.
A force to be reckoned with.
My precious one. you're a phenomenon.
You're a wild storm.
A force to be reckoned with.
My precious one. you're a phenomenon.
Dad!
Sleep. Sleep.
Sleep sooner.
You never back down
A warrior in every fight.
You melt with just one kiss
How do you fall so easily?
You never back down
A warrior in every fight.
You melt with just one kiss
How do you fall so easily?
One kiss. endless teasing
I'll leave you breathless in return.
In every life.
I give myself to you
I'll be your wife in every lifetime.
You've got that aura. my love
I'm under your spell.
You're a wild storm.
A force to be reckoned with.
My precious one. you're a phenomenon.
You're a wild storm.
A force to be reckoned with.
My precious one. you're a phenomenon.
Child. what is your name?
My name is Mathi Malar.
Very good.
What is your father?
My father is a house husband.
Hey!
Not a single man in our legacy
has been a househusband.
Your father is a wrestler too.
Hereafter. if anyone asks you
you should say.
"My father is a wrestler."
- Okay?
- Yeah. okay.
- Very good!
- Your father is here.
Hey. sweetie. what is Uncle saying?
- Uncle was asking my name.
- Is it?
- Shall we go?
- Okay.
I'm leaving. Uncle.
- Bye. Sattam.
- Okay. Veera.
- Go safe.
- Say bye to Uncle.
- Bye. dear.
- Bye. Uncle.
Brother. you're being too mean.
He came all the way to attend the wedding.
but you're clearly ignoring him.
It's been 6 years since you spoke to him.
I'll speak to him when I see the
man he once was in him again.
Let's go!
- Over here.
- Go inside.
It's a huge auditorium.
All hail. Minister!
Welcome. Sir.
Winners of the recently held Tamil Nadu
Inter-Federation tournament…
Will be conferred with.
The Minister is going to
present the award to me.
Awards in this ceremony.
Under the 55 kg category.
the winner is Malithi.
Under the 60 kg category.
the winner is Kavya.
Under the 65 kg category.
the winner is Keerthi.
- Thank you. Sir.
- Mom!
- Is she your daughter?
- Yes. Sir.
Mom. when will they give Dad an award?
Your father will be next.
Please wait.
- I'm heading to the Cadres' Meeting.
- Okay. Sir.
So. you present the awards
to the other winners.
- I'll speak a few words and leave.
- Sure. Sir. I appreciate it.
The winners of the men's category.
and the academy coaches.
will be honored with awards later.
Greetings to all!
Wrestling signifies strength.
A strong society
is essential for our nation.
Compared to North India
people taking up wrestling
is lower in South India.
In Tamil Nadu. specifically.
It's evident that people in the Mettur.
Salem and Erode regions
choose wrestling as their sport.
This interest should
spread across our nation.
Numerous opportunities are available.
Keerthi. to whom
I just presented the shield
she's a mother of a child.
She secured a job in the
Railway Department under sports quota.
She's the face of wrestling
in Tamil Nadu.
Thank you. Sir.
Let her be an inspiration to others.
and many more women
step forward to pursue wrestling.
Also. I come bearing good news.
The upcoming
South Indian Wrestling Tournament
will be held in Coimbatore Academy.
The winners of this tournament
can take part in the next
National Championship held in Delhi.
Bear that in mind and play well.
Thank you! Greetings!
The Minister just quoted:
"You're the face of Tamil Nadu Wrestling."
What's your opinion?
I'm very happy.
The person behind my success…
Veera!
Come over here.
The person behind my success
is my husband.
It is only through his cooperation
and support that I could achieve it.
We could've stayed home in peace.
But you took us by saying
you're getting an award.
Did you get it?
Tell me. did you get it?
Why are you yelling?
Our son might wake up.
Our son went there with the wish
to see his father receive
an award from the Minister.
But the Minister
didn't care a squat about you.
I don't do this
for anyone's praise or recognition.
I do my duty and move on.
Yeah. right. some job you have.
You've been stuck in the same position
for eight years.
But that girl is a fresher.
She got promoted
and moved to the next level.
If I question. you'd say.
"She's a player. so she got her
promotion by winning medals."
"And I'm a coach."
But no one even considers you as a coach.
And she has the nerve to say that
her husband is behind her success.
Another tournament is coming up.
She's going to win again.
After winning.
she'll be promoted to Manager.
What would you do then?
Hold on to the same position
until you retire.
Good morning. Teacher.
Please sit down!
I'm your new class teacher.
My name is Meenu.
Yippee!
Good riddance. spectacles Teacher.
Everyone. please introduce yourselves.
My name is Rishi Arjun.
My father is an accountant.
My name is Bharathi!
Next!
My name is Mathi Malar.
My mother is a wrestler.
My father is also a
wrestler!
Hey. why are you laughing?
Teacher. she's lying.
Her father is not a wrestler.
Her father is a house husband.
Hey. hey. hey! Hey!
What happened. Madam?
You said it's an emergency.
- What's the issue?
- Ask your daughter yourself.
What happened. Sweetie?
Why is your face swollen?
Were these boys?
Ma'am. is this how
you raise your children?
Look how they have beaten my daughter.
Hello. I'm not their mother.
- Then?
- I'm the class teacher.
Class teacher?
I have never seen you before.
- I joined only today.
- Where are you from?
Is this really relevant now?
Sorr... Sorry. Ma'am.
First. look at the boys' faces.
I'm checking.
Let me see.
Damn. it's badly swollen.
Did you both fall?
Are you serious?
If your daughter's face is swollen.
it means they hit her.
But if their faces are swollen.
it means they fell.
I beat them up.
You beat them up?
We're doomed!
Sorry. Madam.
Kids generally get into fights.
Just this once. please excuse her.
You don't have to apologize.
Ask your daughter to apologize.
They're the root cause of the problem.
First. ask them to apologize to me.
Later. I'll apologize.
You've just seen the level
of disrespect she shows.
You'd better take the TC
and leave this school.
TC?
Madam. why would you scare me with a TC?
Teacher. please convince her.
If I take her to another school.
her education will be spoiled.
Hey. apologize to them.
I won't apologize.
Just one sorry. Say it!
- Teacher.
- Ma'am?
Check what the commotion is outside?
- I'll check.
- Let me check.
You please wait here.
I'll check what's happening.
I'll check!
How dare you overtake
our Boss's vehicle?
I was rushing because I was late
to drop the kids at school.
That doesn't mean
you can honk and overtake.
- Hereafter. I won't honk. I'm sorry.
- Hey!
Who the hell are you people?
Why are you creating chaos
inside the school?
Shall I call the Police?
Why don't I call them myself?
How dare you. woman?
You're looking cute
with a cap on your head.
It's not nice
to cause a ruckus at the school.
What do you mean by
I'm wearing a cap?
Does my hair look like a cap to you?
Hi.
Dad!
Kill him!
Hey. take notice.
Still want to mess with me?
Why? Come on!
Get back in the car. you useless fellows.
Start!
Hey. Principal!
How dare you hire a man to beat us up?
I'll handle you later.
I'm challenging you!
Get lost!
No one can mess with the Principal.
I'm not issuing a TC anymore.
As you begged me
I'm letting your daughter
continue in this school.
- Yeah!
- Fantastic!
As your daughter mentioned.
you're not a house husband
but a wrestler.
- Are you a Malayali?
- Yes.
The school called you to report
that our daughter beat up two people.
But you went there
and beat up four people.
The daughter and
father deserve each other.
Darshan and Deepak mocked.
calling Dad a house husband.
That's why I beat them up.
There's nothing wrong with calling him
a house husband.
Let them say it.
Why would you cause problem?
My father is a wrestler just like you.
Check this out.
He defeated a coach!
It's cute for you to think
that what he did was wrestling.
It's just a fight.
That coach spoke ill about me.
So. out of anger. he beat him up.
Back in the hometown.
the President uncle told me.
not to call Dad a house husband.
but to call him a wrestler.
Hey. don't say it.
You must not say
things like that to your mother.
Now I see where my daughter gets it from.
Listen. you may listen to anyone
in this world. but not that man.
He hails from a group
that glorifies patriarchy.
Why would you indulge a child
with such conversation?
She wishes to call her Dad a wrestler.
So be it.
It's our duty as parents
to bring her clarity on matters.
If we fail to do it.
this will be the result.
Listen. dear. your Dad is a house husband.
There's nothing wrong with it.
Understand?
Vani!
Step aside!
Why is he bringing water to our house?
You won't move a muscle.
but you find faults in him.
Annoying!
Goodness gracious. my girl!
I made your favorite brinjal curry.
You'd better finish it all.
Okay?
No way Not this troublemaker.
He's a sly rogue
Who keeps putting on an act.
This is cheating!
Thank you.
Where is he coming from?
I ran out of sugar for coffee.
Why can't you have coffee without sugar?
You have country sugar.
It tastes good!
- Country sugar?
- Hey! Hey! House husband.
My BP shoots up seeing you!
- Are you making chapatis?
- Yes!
Why knead the dough so late?
"Longing to Fly" serial was playing.
I lost track of time watching it.
- Hi. Sir!
- Hello!
I'm going to create an ID
called "House Husband"
I'll keep posting
until he finds an actual job.
In our country. there are fewer
people who work out of passion
than those who work out of humiliation.
Oh!
- House Husband?
- Hey. show me the video.
Veera. your reels are going viral.
Awesome!
Sir. I watched your reels.
They're fantastic!
- Veera!
- Yes. Auntie!
- Your reels are getting a greater reach.
- Thanks!
He's a perfect example of a good husband.
- First let's…
- Comment on the video.
Just because I told our daughter
that you're a house husband
you're started making such reels.
I swear I'm not making them.
I have nothing to do with it.
I don't know who is making them.
Every reel is gaining a lot of views.
Soon we'll be making money from it.
- Shall we continue this as a business?
- It's a good idea.
I ought to!
Among the dishes you make.
which is your wife's favorite dish?
Come with me!
Hey! Hey! House husband.
- It's outstanding. Sir.
- Thank you!
Keerthi will be taking part
in the upcoming South Indian Tournament.
Another player from the same academy
can compete for Team B.
I have suggested your name.
Thank you. Coach!
To hell with your thanks!
This time. you must defeat Keerthi
in the first round.
That's how you'd be thanking me.
First round? How's it possible?
Leave that to me.
Sweetie. who's this at your school
with all that gorgeous thick hair?
Look up! She's my teacher!
Your teacher?
Why is she coming towards me?
I watched your reels.
Very interesting!
You too?
I don't know who's making them. Teacher.
Forget about it.
Where in Kerala are you from?
Cochin!
Are you a Malayali?
Half Malayali!
That's interesting!
What's your name?
Meenu.
Your eyes reveal your name.
If you don't mind.
may I ask you something?
Go ahead!
Are yours original?
What? What do you mean?
No... I meant. is your hair original?
Phew!
Hold it.
I don't mind. Hold it.
- Pull it.
- Sure?
You may pull and check.
- Okay?
- They're original.
I heard that during a fight.
someone pulled your wife's hair
and it came off in front of the crowd.
humiliating her.
So. I reckon you suspect
everyone may have fake hair.
However. don't keep checking people's hair
as you did just now.
I'm leaving!
Hey. Sweetie...
Why is she getting angry?
Let's go together. That'd be best.
Oh. please wait for me to arrive there.
Okay. I'll call you back later.
I'm hanging up.
You speak to your mother
and grandma in Malayalam.
But I don't see you
speaking in Malayalam to Dad.
Why is it. Mom?
Your father doesn't know Malayalam.
Who said so?
He speaks Malayalam well at school.
In Malayalam. you say?
With whom?
He speaks to my Teacher.
- Teacher?
- Yeah. my new Teacher.
Is she a Malayali?
I hear her say she's from Cochin.
Is she married?
No!
How does she look?
She's beautiful.
How beautiful?
She's more beautiful than you.
Enough?
Oh!
How long has this been going on?
It's been just a few days.
Does she have hair?
- Of course. she has hair. Mom.
- Nah!
Like you see thick and fluffy hair
in oil advertisements…
Does she have long hair?
Turn around.
Turn around. I'll show you.
Her hair runs till here.
Now I understand
why the rat is running naked.
And why your Dad is speaking in Malayalam.
Let him come home.
No matter how many years pass by
his brain is still stuck in it.
Oh. God. you've gone mad. Mom.
The moment he sees a woman
with long hair.
What on earth is going on in my house?
So. what are you up to?
How does it matter to you?
You have someone to talk to now.
Go and speak to her.
What are you saying?
I don't understand.
Of course. you wouldn't
understand me anymore.
- What?
- Bloody man.
Loafing around.
Why is she looking at the hair?
Come on. we're running late.
Come on. get on the bike.
Why?
Stop asking questions
and get on the bike.
Hereafter.
I'll be dropping you off at school.
Does that mean
Dad will pick me up in the evening?
Your Dad is an expert pick-up artist!
Get on the bike. girl!
- What happened?
- I don't know.
What did I even pick up?
Get off the bike.
Who is your Teacher?
There she is.
- Everyone. please work hard.
- Yes. Ma'am.
Or else it'll be difficult.
Okay?
- Okay. bye!
- Thank you. Ma'am.
She's not more beautiful than I am.
Hi. Mathi!
Didn't your Dad come to drop you off?
Dad won't be coming.
Hereafter. Mom will be coming.
Let's go!
Why did you stop running?
Enough. Coach.
I am not able to continue.
You'll be taking part
in the South Indian Tournament.
Even if the players are from Andhra.
Karnataka. and Telangana.
the winner will be Keerthi.
You're the only wrestler
who can fight her head-on.
Still. you have lost to her seven times.
She'll win and move to Delhi.
But you'll be left circling locally.
Do you want to go to Delhi
or remain local?
And now. I request our respected
Principal Ma'am to present the prizes.
Niranjan. swimming.
- Well done.
- Hey. Keerthi!
The head of your office is calling you.
Oh! I'll meet her.
G. Prashanth. carrom.
- That's my son.
- That's great!
Hold this and look at the camera.
Very cute!
Where's your daughter?
Didn't she participate in any sport?
Naseer. long jump.
Listen. where's Mathi?
- Surprise!
- Thank you so much. sir and ma'am.
for your lovely gestures.
Finally. our little stars
from first grade. B section.
are ready!
A big applause for all of them!
Hey!
What's this?
Why is she dancing like this?
This is how one could dance to this song.
Your daughter has got great moves!
Super!
Even the laziest parents' kids
are winning prizes in sports.
But you couldn't do it.
How could you not participate
in any sports activity?
But you can dance like a pro
with all that jazz.
I don't know what to do with you.
Kids generally love to dance.
Why are you getting worked up?
I'm not stopping her from dancing.
But she's the daughter
of a State Champion.
It's embarrassing for me when my
daughter doesn't participate in any sport.
She's just in 1st grade now.
Why hurry her with sports?
Sports should be cultivated
from a young age.
If you can't bend when you're 5.
you can't bend when you're 50.
Sir!
Yes. Teacher.
Today. your daughter nailed it.
- Thank you. Teacher.
- She danced well.
Even Simran can't beat her.
I couldn't believe
that she possesses a hidden talent.
Please tell her mother.
She's yelling at us.
You come to the school
only on the Annual Day.
Please don't take me wrong.
Your daughter may be bad at studies…
But she's great at dancing.
If you send her regularly for practice
and train her well
she'll win a title
on the Jodi No.1 reality show.
Did you say she's bad at studies?
You sound as if you're unaware of it.
I thought you were aware of everything.
Teacher. please don't tell her.
Hasn't your husband shown you
her report card yet?
If you aren't aware. let me tell you.
Very talkative!
I'm leaving. Sir.
It's my fault
that I didn't check up on her activities.
From now on. I'll take care of her.
Listen. starting tomorrow.
you'll begin a new life.
Be ready at 06:00 a.m.
New life as in?
Uncle. the South Indian Tournament
is coming up.
I am determined to win it.
I don't have the time to
keep a tab on her activities.
I can't trust anyone. either.
- I understand.
- That's why I asked you to come over.
Good decision!
I forged you into a commendable wrestler.
It's my responsibility
to forge your daughter into a champion.
Are you rattled?
You haven't seen my training.
You'll watch soon!
Hey. ready!
Poor baby!
Hey. Mummy. please.
You know I'm a dummy piece.
- Welcome. Madam.
- My daughter.
Mathimalar. She's in 1st grade.
- You must coach her.
- Sure. I'll coach her.
Does that mean I'm not her coach?
My mother didn't call
you here to train me.
She called you here to be my nanny.
Like ice in the sun.
I couldn't last.
Like jam on a bun
I disappeared without a trace.
Like ice in the sun.
I couldn't last.
Like jam on a bun
I disappeared without a trace.
Mathi! Mathi!
You're late for the training.
Hurry up!
Are you a professional tormentor?
Or are you
Adolf Hitler's granddaughter?
Come on!
NO!
Come on! Come on. fast!
Mom. I'm very tired.
Can we skip training today?
You're a great actor like your father.
Chill. Chill. Chill Mummy Chill
I Say Chill. Chill. Chill
Mummy Chill. Chill. Chill.
- Hurry up! How long would you take?
- Wait! Wait!
Watch out! It's very hot!
Here you go!
Millet ball with onions.
This is your morning diet!
She's too young to be on a diet.
No stone becomes a statue
without enduring the craft of the chisel.
It's obvious the chisel never touched you.
Hey. Mummy please.
Left!
Right!
I scream in pain and ask to be let go.
But she never let go of me.
You're bound to get hurt in wrestling.
Why are you making a big deal out of it?
Dad. is she really my birth mother?
Harry Potter. I'm your daughter
Enough with the torture!
Why does a rabbit need boxing?
Why does a lion need dancing?
Dad. my legs are really hurting a lot.
I don't want to go for training tomorrow.
Please don't say that.
Your mother will get angry.
Why only her?
Even I know how to get angry.
I Say Chill. Chill. Chill
Mummy Chill. Chill. Chill.
Mathi. come!
I'm coming.
Hold your horses!
- What happened. Teacher?
- She's down with a fever.
- Is it?
- Yeah!
You know I'm a dummy piece.
Hey. Mummy please.
She was doing well in the morning.
How come she's down with a fever now?
She complained last night about leg pain.
She was feeling a bit
under the weather in the morning.
I reckon her legs weren't hurting
while dancing.
Didn't you use to say. "When we
do something we love. it doesn't hurt."
Oh!
So. she likes dancing but not wrestling.
Right?
Whether she likes it or not
is the issue here.
Is she learning wrestling at 6
to become a champion?
Why are you torturing the child?
Torturing. you say?
No one can become a champion overnight.
It takes years of penance to achieve.
In China. they start training
as early as age 3 or 4.
That's why that country tops the Olympics.
But in India. parents like you
coddle their children…
And that results in no medals
for our country.
I'll call you later.
Please bear this in mind.
Times have changed.
The current generation
takes everything lightly.
However. when they encounter
a minor setback. they can't bear it.
Willpower has gone for a toss!
Only sports can instill discipline
and willpower in a person.
Look. Veera. I'm repeating myself.
enough spoiling her
with your love and pampering.
If we let it continue.
she'll turn into you.
I'll take care of her education
and career.
You handle the household.
Veera. is there a problem?
She went overboard. Coach.
She's accusing me of saying
our daughter will become like me.
Why can't she turn out like me?
Let it go. Veera.
Stress is the root cause of the problem.
What are you saying?
See. It's not just Keerthi…
Any sports champion
experiences high stress.
However. those who can't handle the stress
have disappeared from sports
without a trace.
I don't understand what you're saying.
You see. Keerthi gets angry a lot.
You're right. Coach.
Stress is the main factor behind anger.
When you get angry. your BP shoots up.
If BP shoots up.
it'll cause more health problems.
If that happens.
then she must forget about wrestling.
Oh. no!
Of course!
Health is important for players.
That's crucial!
Now what do we do. Coach?
Matches are lined up for her.
How do we bring down
her stress and anger?
If you attend counseling.
everything will be alright.
What's counseling?
And where do we attend it?
There's a famous psychiatrist
named Benjamin Kutty.
You guys consult him.
and everything will be alright.
Tell it's for the child.
Only then will Keerthi step out.
You're right. Coach!
You two. please step outside for a while.
Why?
I don't know what's going to happen.
Why are you sending them outside?
- They both need counseling.
- I will get to it.
Please sit down.
Do you know what Sigmund Freud quoted?
"Anger is a messenger."
It means…
Anger is nothing but a messenger.
It's trying to convey something to us.
Doctor. why are you explaining it to me?
The water inside the pressure cooker…
Keeps boiling up like this.
If the cooker is faulty…
It'll explode!
It bursts!
Hey. idiot!
Have you gone mad?
Don't you get it? I have no issues.
Every patient who comes here
claims the same.
Once we start the treatment
everything will be fine.
- Get lost!
- Come on. catch her!
No. no. no!
Don't be silly like a kid!
Hey. hold her properly.
- Let go of me.
- It's nothing. It's a small injection.
Oh. no!
Let go of me!
What do you think of yourself?
I took you to a psychiatrist
to get your anger under control.
There you broke his furniture
and caused chaos.
So that's your plan
to control my anger?
Does my concern for my daughter
look like anger to you?
Dear. calm down.
Didn't you lie that it's for our child?
Our child has no issues.
It's you who has been
short-tempered lately.
And your anger is affecting her.
A child should be afraid of
at least one parent.
She's not afraid of you.
That's why I'm being the strict parent.
Just because you're a champion
doesn't mean you're right.
Life is different from sports.
To me. sports and life are the same.
I'm saying this to benefit your career.
Why don't you understand?
You'll understand when you face defeat.
You never seem to understand.
What did you just say now?
"I'll understand when I face defeat."
So. you want me to lose?
Isn't that what you want?
That's not how I meant it.
What did you mean then?
Keerthi. let it go!
- He did not mean it that way…
- He…
- Did you not hear him?
- I did!
"I'll understand when I face defeat."
Do you want me to lose?
- Answer me!
- He said it in a flow.
That doesn't mean he could say anything.
I think I'm going mad!
That's why I took you to the psychiatrist.
As it is.
being a husband to a woman isn't easy.
I can't even begin to imagine
if it's a sportswoman…
Hmm… I wonder how you manage.
Why don't we try another technique?
There's a medicine in Ayurveda to
bring anger and stress under control.
It doesn't matter.
She wouldn't come anywhere now.
She doesn't have to come anywhere.
Then how's it possible?
It's 3.500 rupees for the medicine.
How do we take this?
You can mix it in your food.
Or you could mix it in the milk.
How does it work
when we consume this medicine?
For that. you must study
medicine for 5 years.
Would you like to?
Yes. Doctor. how are you?
You met them at the temple. is it?
Bye. Doctor.
Only after visiting
other rituals would follow.
Let me know how you got lucky.
I've been trying for 15 years.
Aren't you eating?
I'll eat later. You eat now.
Here. have some egg.
It tastes good!
Keerthi!
It's a good thing you started
training your daughter at an early age.
Very good!
But my husband is against it.
Don't take me wrong.
But your husband is uneducated.
We should make him understand
the importance of it.
Lock. lock me.
Move quickly. Ready?
Good! Good!
Keep moving. Keep Moving.
Concentrate! Concentrate!
Isn't it unrefined cane sugar?
Then why does it taste weird?
It's organic.
That's how it will taste.
Keerthi. your lunch is ready.
What happened?
This is our hereditary plate.
Hereditary plate?
Good. good. good. Come on!
What happened. Keerthi?
Are you okay?
What are you mixing in the milk?
For the past two days.
my stomach has been upset.
Me too. I have diarrhea.
Let me try if this helps.
It's delicious!
Come on. lock him.
Lock him!
Please let me practice with girls.
Keerthi not only practices in the academy.
But at home.
she practices with her husband.
That's why she is able to
win matches against girls.
Do you wish to go to Delhi or not?
Wait I'll get it for you.
She's not eating.
Do we have pickles?
Wait a second.
- Where did I keep it?
- What is this?
It's a herbal powder.
Mathi often catches a cold.
It's for her immunity.
Oh! Why did you store it
in a ceramic jar?
If we leave it outside.
ants will spoil it.
- So. I stored it in there.
- Oh!
Here you go.
That was a close call.
Coach. the medications are working well.
Let's go!
Wait. I'm getting a call.
Who's calling?
Hello!
Yeah. it's me. Veera.
When?
Okay. I'll think about it.
Who was it. Dad?
A cooking show is taking place
in Coimbatore tomorrow.
If I win this competition
I will get the "Best Cook Award"
of this district.
They chose me as a contestant
based on my Behindwoods interview.
Hey. that's great!
That cooking show is my favorite.
I cook well.
Take me as well. Please!
Unfortunately. even I can't make it.
Keerthi has a match tomorrow.
Will Dad appear on TV?
Definitely!
That show is every household's favorite.
And your Dad will appear
on every TV in every home.
Why not. Dad?
You go ahead and take part in the show.
Hey. it's Mom's match tomorrow.
Mom has matches all year.
Moreover. it's not like it's final.
It's just the first round.
For me. you must take part in this show
and win a prize. Dad.
Why are you so enthused about it?
So. I could ask Deepak and Darshan.
"My Dad was on TV.
Were your Dads ever on TV?"
Everyone's got their own agenda.
Promise me that you'll win the prize.
Do it!
Fine. no need for a promise.
I will do my best
to take part in the show.
Okay?
Let's tell Mom about it.
Don't tell her yet.
If you do. she won't let you go.
If we don't tell her.
she'll yell at me when she sees me on TV.
When she yells. we'll handle it.
What are you guys whispering about?
Why aren't we leaving yet?
You take Keerthi and go ahead.
I'll bring Mathi and follow you later.
Okay!
Dear. let's go.
Let them go first.
- She left! Let's go now.
- Come on. let's go!
Keerthi!
We're getting ready to watch your match.
You must rock it today.
Thanks. Auntie.
- All the best. Keerthi!
- Bye!
Hi. Hello. Vanakkam!
You're watching Your Kovai Kitchen.
Taste of Coimbatore.
- Welcome. Sir.
- Where do I leave my phone?
- Leave it here.
- Over here?
Let's go!
And the final contestant for the day…
Let's welcome. Veera
and Meenu!
Not bad. you came to our show
with your wife and kid.
Oh. she's not my wife.
- She's my daughter's class teacher.
- Oh!
Why did you bring your
daughter's teacher to stir gravy?
She's here for moral support.
They have a good understanding.
But it may cause a
misunderstanding in their family.
South Indian Wrestling Tournament
is about to begin.
First to fight are Regina in red tracks
and Keerthi in Blue tracks.
Come on. start!
The umpire has blown the whistle
to kick start the fight.
- Come on. Keerthi.
- Both are putting up an equal fight.
- Keerthi. come on!
- Which fighter will score the first point?
Don't let go of the grip.
Slam her!
That's about it!
Keerthi is leading by 4 points
after using the back throw technique.
Keerthi continues to show her prowess.
She's leading with 4 points.
Your time starts now!
Hey. everyone. make sure
you're with your own wives.
Here you go.
The vegetables are out there.
Here. wear it.
- Both are attacking each other.
- Hold her down.
Regina is going for a flip throw.
Regina did a flip throw
and scored 4 points. tying the score.
Nice one!
Keerthi and Regina are at 4 point each.
Red. 4. Blue. 4.
- Keerthi is trying to attack.
- Come on!
- Regina has locked Keerthi from behind.
Now Keerthi makes her counter move…
- Keerthi is now leading…
- That was an amazing slam!
Not sure why Keerthi is staggering.
Only 1 minutes and 30 seconds are left.
Right now Keerthi is at 8 points.
And Regina is at 4 points.
Wow! It smells yummy!
Yes. I ground it in Ammi (grinder).
- She meant yummy. not Ammi.
- Dad. hurry up.
You have the last 30 minutes left
to finish cooking.
Hurry up. Teacher.
Oh. no!
Hey. hey!
Careful!
Dear!
Attack her!
Attack!
Keerthi's uncle is encouraging her.
Don't lose your grip.
Regina mustering up her strength.
with front lock and threw her away.
With this Regina has gained 4 points.
Once again the points are equal at 8 each.
Regina once again does the Dhobi Throw.
Regina scores another 4 points.
making her score 12 now.
Get up! Get up!
Regina is in the lead now.
Oh. no!
Keerthi!
Get up!
Will the undefeated champion
Keerthi recover?
Time has ended
and the umpire has blown the whistle.
Based on the points Regina has been
declared as the winner of this match.
Yes!
Oh. no!
Don't cry!
We'll make it up in the next tournament.
What happened. Keerthi?
This is not your game!
It's very disappointing.
I don't understand either.
She's unlikely to lose like this.
Let it go. dear.
- Coach!
- Yeah!
No! There's been a mistake.
This report does not belong to Keerthi.
Coach. this is Keerthi's report.
Why? Why happened?
Players usually undergo a dope test.
Keerthi's report states
there were steroids in her bloodstream.
Keerthi. did you take any painkillers
over the past couple of days?
Did you make any changes
to your food supplements?
No. Sir.
She follows a home-cooked diet.
Does that mean there were any changes
made in the home-cooked diet?
Son-in-law is the one who cooks at home.
He…
Where's Veera?
How come he's not here?
Wait!
It's ringing. but he's not answering.
I wonder where he went.
What are you looking for?
Tell me. I'll find it for you.
Keerthi!
Why are there so many packets?
What's this?
Herbal powder.
Ask them to test this thing.
I would like to know what's in it.
Your time is up!
Here. take a look at it.
Look!
Your suspicion was right.
Steroids has been mixed in that powder.
What happened. Keerthi?
The report says it's positive.
It tastes weird.
It's organic.
It's supposed to taste like it.
I can't believe Veera could do this.
He's the first person to wish
for Keerthi's victory.
How could you all suspect him?
Hey. shut up! Take a look at this.
I had many videos.
so I missed out on this.
Look at him mixing meds in food.
What more proof do we need?
He'd be the first to show up
at Keerthi's matches.
But he did not come today.
Also. he's not answering his phone.
Your father is indeed a house husband.
If it continues she'll end up like you.
You'll understand when you face defeat.
He could not face you.
So. he went into hiding.
- I called him many times.
- Sir!
He didn't answer.
Sir. he did not disappear.
Look over here.
Here. taste this as well.
- Please try this salad.
- I don't eat vegetarian food today.
What are these dishes called?
Raw Tamarind Rasam.
Fish fry. parboiled red rice.
Millet ball. Chintamani chicken gravy.
Coconut cakes and pickled chicken.
In today's competition.
everyone did their best.
The competition was tough.
But in a competition.
there's only one winner.
Veera and Meenu
are the title winners today.
Yayy!
Oh. no!
Yes!
Veera. how do you manage
to cook such tasty dishes?
My wife Keerthi is my inspiration to cook.
I want my wife to scale heights in sports.
So I sent her to the ground
and took charge of the kitchen.
I researched nutritious food
and started cooking for her.
No matter what I cook
she eats it without asking any questions.
She trusts me a lot.
- But you broke her trust.
- To be blessed with a husband like Veera
his wife is a lucky person.
All the best. Veera!
- You're the real winner.
- Keerthi!
Thank you! Thank you!
Keerthi. I won a title
in the cooking show.
They gave me the "Best Cook" award.
After what you did.
how dare you show off your award?
- What are you looking at?
- What's happening?
What happened? What did I do?
You don't know what you did?
Hand it to me.
See what you've done.
At the very first round
of the South India Wrestling Tournament
wrestler Keerthi lost to wrestler Regina.
How did you lose?
A blood test taken
after the match reported
that Keerthi had taken
a performance drug.
This news has rattled the world of sports.
Performance drug?
Wrestler Keerthi is banned for a year
for using a performance drug.
The Sports Federation has issued an order.
Keerthi. what does it mean?
Keerthi!
Damn you!
Isn't this what you expected?
When you said
only defeat will teach me a lesson…
I thought you said it in a fit of anger.
But I never expected you to do this to me.
I did not. Keerthi.
In the end.
you still are holding on to that male ego.
Your male ego
has ruined my career for good.
How do I explain it to you?
Keethy. I did not…
Who would in this world…
Would mix steroids in his wife's food?
Steroid?
I don't want to see you anymore.
- Go away!
- Keerthi. hear me out.
I didn't know how steroids got mixed
into that medicine.
Leave my daughter and me alone.
Sweetie!
Keerthi! Keerthi!
Keerthi. I don't know
what really happened.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Keerthi!
I thought Veera was a good husband.
How could he do this to you?
When it comes to a husband.
there is no good or bad.
A husband is always a bad person.
He always put up an act
encouraging the wife
and stabbed her in the back
at her crucial moment in life.
Well done. Son!
Until now. I misunderstood you.
That you've become henpecked
like the rest of the men.
But you struck her at the right time.
I'm proud of you!
You got it wrong. Uncle.
I did not do it on purpose.
Even if you did it on purpose.
there's nothing wrong with it.
Women like her deserve this behavior.
Truly deserve it.
We had a grandfather. Kanniappan.
He used to work in Burma.
You may have heard about him.
- I have!
- Yeah!
How do you think his wife died?
The Karupatti Halwa he brought
every time he returned from Burma…
Used it as a spread on the bread
laced with poison and killed her.
To be honest.
I'm just afraid of the Police; If not.
I would've poisoned my wife long ago.
But you did it!
You proved you're that
from Kanniappan's bloodline.
I appreciate it!
A husband may endure anything.
But he will never endure
his wife surpassing him in life.
It's a different case with the wives.
They always wish their husbands would earn
more than other men and achieve success.
Because wives are always the martyrs.
Who is a martyr?
Who the hell is a martyr?
The men who toil through
blood and sweat every day.
facing humiliation from
complete strangers.
and still carrying on
to provide for their families
this is not the story of one man.
but of millions of men.
Do you call these men martyrs?
Sitting idle at home.
eating three square meals a day.
binge-watching serials.
liking random Instagram posts.
and growing as stout as a stone mortar.
Or do you call these women martyrs?
My husband said taking care
of the kids is a mother's job.
Really?
Then why do I need you in this house?
I asked him to leave and divorced him.
- Divorce?
- Of course!
In this world.
if a dog is praised for its gratitude.
then a husband is branded as ungrateful.
- Do you agree?
- Yes!
Be strong. We're with you.
Your husband will claim he gave
you the medicine to calm your temper.
Don't even let him near you.
Sattam. that Ayurvedic doctor gave
her medicine to control her temper.
I have never seen a fool worse than you.
- Why would you say that?
- What do you expect?
You believed that a medicine
could control a wife's temper.
How do I even begin to explain?
They may even find a cure
for AIDS and cancer in the future.
Humanity can split atoms
and explore galaxies.
but a wife's anger remains unsolved.
If they ever achieve a breakthrough.
humanity might go extinct
like the dinosaurs.
For the first time since you became
a lawyer. you spoke like a true one.
Have a drink!
- Cheers!
- Cheers. Brother!
Oh. God. these men!
Veera! Veera!
Freshen up. Let's eat.
I don't know what happened. Auntie.
That doesn't mean
you leave your wife and kid behind.
Do you know what she accused me of?
I'm... I'm still holding on to male ego.
And that I destroyed her career.
Do you know how it hurt me?
You did it for her well-being.
but it backfired.
The time and circumstances
are against you.
You claim that you're unaware
of what happened.
Then. how do you expect
Keerthi to understand?
Go. meet her and speak to her.
Console her!
You carry on. I'll wait here.
In a day. everything went topsy-turvy.
You've become the common enemy
of women everywhere.
In the game of Snakes and Ladders.
the ladder takes you up.
However. the snake
will be sitting right next to it.
Stopping yapping like an idiot.
- Where are my wife and kid?
- Idiot?
Why is the house locked?
She went to her mother's house
in Palakkad.
- Why don't you mind your business?
- He asked.
- Why are you acting like a fool?
- Fool?
- Why are you yelling at me?
- Dare you I'd leave to my mother's place.
- Won't I get angry?
- Get inside the house.
If you go over there now.
it'll only fuel more anger.
Let's not go. Veera.
- One more bit.
- Enough!
I thought men from Tamil Nadu
are good and I got her married.
But he ruined everything.
What's happening. God?
- Shut up old woman.
- Hey!
You don't know anything about my father.
You shouldn't disrespect elders.
Please eat.
Dad!
Keerthi… Keerthi!
Keerthi.
Keerthi. wait a minute.
You already ruined it all.
Why are you here now?
I did not ruin anything. Granny.
It was unintentional.
Why haven't you invited him
into the house?
- Please come in. son-in-law.
- Brother. what are you doing?
Hey. stop right there!
Don't you have any shame?
Are you planning to host a feast for him?
- Hey. stop talking nonsense!
- Brother. you shut up!
You ought to have him arrested
for what he did to Keerthi.
Have him arrested?!
- I dare you to file a complaint!
- Calm down.
Did you bring a lawyer to threaten us?
I will bring a lawyer too.
- Listen...
- He did not come here as a lawyer.
He's here as my friend.
Sure. he's your friend!
But isn't he also a lawyer?
He's always roaming around
wearing a uniform.
- Hey. don't you dare disrespect me!
- Damn you!
- What are you…
- Oh. so you want me to respect you?!
- That's how I'll speak to you!
- Please hear me out.
- Uncle. calm down.
- I'll disrespect you even more!
If you are real men…
Keerthi. what's wrong with you?
Why don't you stop them?
There's quite a scene outside!
- Hey. watch your mouth!
- Uncle. please don't!
Uncle. please calm down.
- Please hear me out.
- Get out of here!
Oh. God!
- Uncle...
- Hey!
Son-in-law. why did you slap him?
I didn't slap him on purpose.
I slapped him by mistake.
"I mixed the medicine by mistake.
I slapped him by mistake."
How many more mistakes
will you make unintentionally?
I came here seeking peace
for a couple of days.
But you couldn't leave me alone!
Keerthi. please hear me out once...
I've had enough of trusting you.
I'm not ready to trust you anymore.
Don't create any trouble.
Get out of here.
The number you have dialed
is presently not reachable.
Did you go to the clinic?
Yeah. there's been a mix-up
with the medicines.
Only if the Doctor explains it to her
will Keerthi believe me.
The clinic is locked.
and the doctor is missing too.
Since Keerthi's case
became sensational news.
I think the doctor went underground
to avoid a police case.
He's a very famous Doctor in that area.
Even I'm confused about
what went wrong with the medicines.
Coach. please explain the confusion
about the medicines to Keerthi.
She would believe you.
Sure. Veera!
I'll speak to Keerthi.
Please go home.
Okay. Coach.
Who gave you permission to go to Palakkad?
You've gone from begging your wife
to begging her entire family.
If we're the ones in the wrong.
we have to be submissive. Uncle.
You've gone mad!
Husbands should be dominant!
If we keep being submissive
the wives will bury the husbands
deep underground.
How do you suggest we fix this?
When a fight breaks out
between a husband and a wife
staying silent
will eventually solve the problem.
There's nothing we could do.
Only in our country
does the husband-and-wife quarrel
continue like local riots.
Why do husband and wife
often end up fighting?
You're very innocent.
Isn't it obvious?
- Which is our country?
- India.
- Did India and Germany ever fight?
- No!
Did India and Australia ever fight?
- Who do we fight with?
With Pakistan and China.
Where are they located?
- They're our neighboring countries.
- That's the issue!
When we're closer. it's always an issue.
It does not necessarily have to be
India-Pakistan or India-China.
It's enough if you're a husband and wife.
- Brother. did you hear the news?
- What news?
In the upcoming elections. the Panchayat
President seat is reserved for women.
Who gave them the right to do it?
I'm the only President of this Panchayat.
I will contest in the elections.
I challenge the election commission.
Stop talking like an idiot.
Only ladies can contest
in the ladies' constituency.
Do you mean
that I have become a woman?
If you speak nonsense.
they'll lock you up in prison.
Let's contest
from a different constituency.
- That's part of Tamil Nadu as well.
- Yeah. right!
No one from our constituency would
vote for you because of your behavior.
Yet you expect votes
from different constituencies.
Hey. we'll bribe them with money.
briyani. and liquor.
That won't work out.
I've been in power for the past 10 years.
What do I do now?
Why don't you let your wife contest?
All the women will vote for her.
Do you expect me
to make my wife the President
and then stay home like an imbecile?
I'd rather drink poison and die.
Auntie will be the President for namesake.
But you will be calling the shots.
This is what's happening
in many ladies' constituencies.
What do you say. Sattam?
Veera is right about it.
Our only choice now is your wife.
There's no other option.
Welcome. Uncle.
This way.
Please sign this form.
Do you know how to sign.
or would a thumbprint do?
- I know how to sign.
- Fine. go ahead.
Don't sign incorrectly
and humiliate my legacy.
I have to teach her everything.
- Hello?
- Dad!
- My ill fate.
- Mathi!
- How are you?
- We're back home.
- I have to go to school tomorrow.
- Yeah!
So. Mom brought me back home.
- Did you eat?
- Yeah. I ate.
Hey. Mathi. who are you speaking to?
I'm speaking to my friend Vinoth.
I don't trust you. Let me check.
Come on. give me my phone.
You were telling the truth.
Fine. speak to him.
Okay. it's getting very crowded out here.
I'll meet you during lunch break tomorrow.
- Did you call me a crowd?
- Okay?
Okay.
Dad!
Come to me. dear!
Sambhar rice! Here. take a bite.
Eat faster.
Or lunch break will end soon.
Why don't you have a spoon as well?
- Why?
- Eat!
There's no salt.
This is nothing. Dad.
In the morning. another mayhem happened.
Mayhem. you say?
Hurry up!
Hey. what are you doing?
When I drop the idlis my father makes
it'll stick to the plate.
But Mom's idlis are bouncing.
Is it an idli or a ball?
Where's chutney?
There's no chutney.
Sugar will do. Eat now.
Dad used to make two chutneys for idlis.
Coconut chutney and tomato chutney.
Be thankful that I'm making idlis for you
despite my busy schedule.
And you're demanding 4 chutneys.
I don't care if you eat or not.
You're overdoing it.
Idlis with sugar are tasty.
Good combination.
Mom's cooking is horrible. Dad.
Please get back with Mom
so that I can eat tasty food.
- Why didn't you finish your lunch?
- I did finish it.
You haven't touched your lunch.
Oh. no!
My friend brought chicken.
so I ate that.
- Chicken made you forget sambhar rice.
- Oh. God. I'm caught.
I woke up early to make you lunch.
This is for you and this is for me.
Yayy!
How do you manage to eat that food?
It's my wife's cooking.
It'll be delicious.
- Please have some. Teacher.
- No. Teacher. that's my Mom's cooking.
Hey. don't be a brat!
Mom. what are you even doing?
You can't even braid my hair.
Dad used to create art with my braids.
If you bring up your father again.
I'll kill you.
Dad. my foot!
Here you go!
Isn't her mother coming here
every day to pick her up?
Why don't you talk to her?
If she knows I'm coming here.
she won't send Mathi to school.
Please vote for the Bucket symbol…
Vote for Bucket symbol!
Vote for Bucket and support Padma...
President. you're here
to ask to vote for your wife.
Yes!
But if you have your nephew by your side.
who betrayed his wife
how do you expect us to vote?
Uncle!
Son! If you're here. no
woman is going to vote for us.
You better scram from here.
We'll discuss the rest at home.
Step down!
Your wish is our wish.
Please support Padma Rathinam
and vote for her.
I sincerely request you to support us.
Hail. Chief!
Thank you all!
Where is the President?
I don't know Hindi.
Talk to me in English.
Where is Padma?
Why is he asking about my wife?
Brother. BDO has come down.
He might report to the higher officials.
Ask your wife to come right away.
Why should she come here?
I'm the President here.
Ask him to talk to me.
Just for a day. It's a formality.
Ask her to come.
Here. take it.
Come.
It's my wife. Padma.
Speak to her.
Do you know the key roles and
responsibilities of a Panchayat President?
- Why not?
- No. why not?
She's uneducated.
Administrative functions.
Financial Management
of the village administration.
Welfare and development programs.
And dispute resolution.
and also public representation.
Panchayat President
is a sole executive power
which holds the integrity
and the development of the Village.
Okay. okay. if you know so much
why would you let someone else
run the office?
You're well aware of how our system works.
What would women do in this situation?
Hey. she's speaking in Hindi.
I'm yet to recover from the shock
of her speaking English.
I thought she never studied
beyond 4th grade.
But she's excelling in every language.
Come in.
Step aside.
Please sit.
PRESIDENT.
Sign!
R. PADMA
Who is he?
My husband.
House husband?
Yes!
For the next 5 years.
he must not step inside this office.
If he steps in. we'll get him arrested.
- Understand? All the best!
- Alright!
Thank you.
How come you spoke to him
in both Hindi and English?
You'd better tell me the truth.
How far are you educated?
Speak up!
- B.A.
- Who's PA?
- B.A. English Literature.
- What?!
B.A. English Literature. she says.
Hail. Padma!
- Sweetie!
- Hi. Dad. how are you?
I'm doing well. How are you?
I'm doing okay. Did you eat?
I ate! What about you?
I ate four idlis.
Hey…
Did you finish your homework?
Who is she speaking to?
She's speaking to her classmate. Vinoth.
- I'll call you later.
- What happened?
Come here.
Hand me the phone.
Hand it over right now.
Hand it. Mathi.
- Come on!
- Give it to me.
I told you right. It's Vinoth.
I've been checking on her daily.
Come on. dear. tell your mother.
When your mother asks.
you must hand it over right away.
Why did you hang up?
Was your uncle around you?
- Oh. no. you girl!
- Hello? Hello?
Sweetie!
Hello?
Is this how you check on her?
How long has this been going on?
I'm speaking to you.
Speak up!
I'm talking to my father.
How does it bother you?
How does it bother me?
For what your father did to me.
I should've divorced him.
First. divorce me.
I don't like to live with you anymore.
You don't like to live with me?
- Did you see how insensitive she is?
- You're right.
It's all because of this phone.
I'll see how you're going to speak now.
Oh. no! Hey!
Hey! Little devil!
The number you're trying to call
is currently not reachable. Please try...
Get off the bike.
Bye.
Mathi!
Sweetie!
Dad!
Hey. what happened?
Why are you crying?
Mom and I got into a fight.
And Mom beat me.
- Did she beat you?
- Yes!
I called you last night. remember.
So. she broke the phone.
Oh. no!
It's Uncle's phone. so don't bother.
I'm not going back to Mom anymore.
You come and get me
in the evening after school.
Just a few days. dear.
Everything will be alright.
Then. take me out somewhere.
I want to spend time with you.
Now? What about school?
Let's bunk school!
- Bunk?
- Who's bunking school?
Teacher!
Teacher. you see.
she and her mother got into a fight.
- She's very upset...
- So?
If you grant her half a day permission
I'll take her out. calm her down.
and bring her back during the lunch break.
Please. Teacher.
- Fine. bring her back soon.
- Thank you. Teacher.
My sweet little darling
Smiles and dances playfully.
The thunderous sky joins the rhythm.
Her little feet
Hopping along in delight.
Even the breeze sings a folk tune.
You're the moonlight of this home.
You're the rainbow
That walked into my life.
You're my mirror image. my love.
The magic in your eyes lingers on me.
My daughter. my treasure.
Let's leap with joy and share stories.
Let's leap with joy
And share stories.
The moment hunger strikes.
She starts demanding attention.
Challenge her. she'll fight back.
One moment. and it's all forgotten.
A mother's warmth by my side.
Resting in the comfort of my lap.
Curled up there from dawn to dusk.
Playful toes upon my forehead.
She cheers me on When I'm down.
You're my mirror image. my love.
The magic in your eyes lingers on me.
My daughter. my treasure.
Let's leap with joy
And share stories.
My daughter. my treasure.
Let's leap with joy
And share stories.
Daughters are always a father's pet.
That's how they'll react.
Don't overthink.
Wash your hands. and we'll have lunch.
Go!
She was angry. so I don't know if she ate.
Let me feed her and console her.
If I don't. I'll feel terrible.
- You carry on.
- Okay.
Auntie!
Mathi did not attend the class today.
- She was absent.
- What do you mean?
I went to her class
during the second period
but she was not in the classroom.
I dropped her off myself in the morning.
Please call her class teacher. Meenu.
Did her daughter. Mathi Malar
make it to school today?
- You see…
- Why are you hesitating?
She did come to school. Ma'am.
But she did not attend any classes.
What do you mean by that?
Where the hell did she go?
So. you let her go with her Dad?
Ma'am. she was very upset and dull.
- So…
- It doesn't matter how she is feeling.
Are you her mother. or am I?
- Ma'am...
- Keerthi. I insisted on taking her out.
It's not her fault.
I dropped her off at the school.
Who gave her the right
to send her off with him?
Is this how you run your school?
Ma'am. don't be loose with your words.
She did not send her off
with some stranger.
It's her father who took her out.
Keep your familial fights
limited to your family.
Please don't drag it to school.
- Mathi. let's go.
- I'm not coming.
Mathi. please come with me.
Don't get me worked up.
I won't come with you.
You'll beat me.
I won't beat you. Come with me.
You sound very angry.
I'm not angry. Come with me.
I'm going with Dad.
- Go with your Mom.
- I won't go with her.
- Keerthi. I'll bring her. You leave.
- You better come with me.
- Didn't I tell you earlier?
- I'll bring her Keerthi.
- Not to leave the school.
- I'll bring her.
- Why did you go out?
- Why are you beating her?
- Don't beat her.
Don't beat. Keerthi.
Please don't beat her.
- Hey. Keerthi!
- Are you coming with me or not?
Keerthi. don't beat her.
Don't you hear me?
Keerth...
Kee...
Sorry.
You slapped her in front of many people.
I did not do it on purpose.
She was beating our daughter.
I couldn't control myself
and raise my hand at her.
It's her daughter
and she has every right to.
That does not give you the right
to slap her.
What you did isn't justified.
He hit his wife.
What's wrong with it?
Isn't he her husband?
What if she slaps him back?
Do you think she can't?
- Isn't she a wrestler?
- Why not?
Time have changed.
Wait a minute.
I don't want lunch.
Make it just for yourself.
I'll be done with the meeting
only in the evening.
Crisps are drying on the terrace.
Bring them down before it rains.
Also. bring water to the cows.
Most importantly.
don't sleep with the doors open.
Stray dogs will enter the house.
Auntie will be the President for namesake.
But you will be calling the shots.
Veera. come with me.
I want to talk to you.
Go. go!
You've already ruined it for me.
Go!
To hell with him!
I wonder when she learned to drive.
I'm not sure what else I have to
endure in my life.
He slapped our daughter in public.
Does he think no one would question him?
Your daughter is crying her eyes out.
But you're sitting idle
like a statue out here.
Mom. she's not crying
because her husband slapped her.
She's crying because she hit her daughter.
I shouldn't have hit her.
I was angry with my husband
and took it out on her.
Poor thing. Mathi.
She must be in pain.
The conflict between you two
began over how to raise your child.
Now you have blew up the problem.
The biggest challenge for parents
is raising a child.
But if you don't raise the child right…
All the parents drown in guilt.
That we did not raise the children well.
We pampered them too much.
To avoid those regrets.
parents raise them strictly.
VILLAGE HEAD
KEELA AMBUR PANCHAYAT.
Listen. Veera.
I don't have children.
If I had.
I would've raised it the way Keerthi is.
In today's world. we must raise
our daughters to be strong.
We should start teaching them martial arts
or wrestling when they're 6 years old.
We see a lot of news day in and out.
While going to study.
or work. or going out
every day. women face danger
in many forms.
Parents can't accompany them everywhere.
The Police won't be
at guard everywhere. either.
Women have to save themselves.
Anyone who learns Karate during
childhood doesn't become a master in it.
It's just for self defense.
Similarly. wrestling.
Once she grows up.
if she feels wrestling is not her calling
she can move on to pursue something else.
But the wrestling she learned
will protect her for life.
Dad. why are you not sleeping?
Nothing much. dear.
You seemed happy
when you came to see me at school.
I'm here with you now.
but you don't seem happy.
Why?
I'm happy. dear.
But Mom will be sad without you.
She won't be suffering. though.
She does not like me.
I'm sure she must be having fun.
Do you think so?
Shall I tell you a story?
Is it a story of a lion or a fox?
It's neither!
It's a story about a Dora Baby like you.
Dora Baby? Please tell me.
Dora Baby was five years old.
How does she look?
She is beautiful and cute like you.
That baby was very interested in wrestling
at that young age.
She had her first match at 10 years old.
At 15 she was a school champion.
Hereafter. you should not
take part in wrestling.
- Focus on your studies.
- Her father restricted her.
But she did not pay heed to her father.
She started wrestling in college
without her parents' knowledge.
She was old enough for marriage.
But could not find a match.
They rejected her
because she is a wrestler.
For the women of our country.
family comes first.
On seeing her father's health.
she quit wrestling and got married.
Her husband was not understanding.
Once he knew she was a wrestler.
he asked her to leave.
Dear. listen...
Later. he challenged her
to a wrestling match.
Only then did he realize
wrestling is a tough sport.
And how much she has
sacrificed in her life.
Despite having no support from her family.
she excelled in wrestling.
It must not go to waste. right?
So. he decided to support her dreams.
That's when she gave birth to a child.
After giving birth.
continuing wrestling is tough.
The body and health won't be the same.
Still. she overcame it
and continued to pursue wrestling.
The child had mother's milk for 2 years.
She used to pump milk into the
feeding bottle and head to training.
She once went to Chandigarh
for a two-month training camp.
Bye!
Back home the child was crying
without mother's milk.
During training.
she suffered from breast engorgement.
To cope with the engorgement.
she would express her breast milk
in the bathroom and resume training.
I am going to quit wrestling.
I can't stop thinking about our daughter.
You must not waste your talent.
You continue to train.
I'll take responsibility of our child.
Poor thing. that mother.
She must've suffered
being away from her child.
Where are the mother and child now?
Mom Dora is at her house.
And Baby Dora is with me right here.
Wait. were you telling me
my mother's story all along?
My golden girl.
The treasure of my heart.
I long to see your innocent face.
My precious girl. my treasure!
I long to hear
Your sweet. endearing voice.
Oh. dear! Oh. dear!
My dear friend who playfully quarrels
With me every day.
My dear friend.
Oh. dear! Oh. dear!
You're the sweet friend who defeats me
Without even saying a word.
Tears surge within me like the sea.
Come be the shore
That brings me home.
The night scorches the sky within me.
Come. little moon.
And shine beside me.
Ma'am. courier!
What is this?
You wanted me to quit wrestling.
I did not listen to you.
Now. I'm pushing my daughter
to pursue wrestling.
But she is refusing it.
And she's interested in dancing.
It is the duty of parents to understand
what their child is passionate about.
Not to impose our passion on to our child.
I learnt it from you. my dear.
But you.
Sports gave me everything I have today.
My self confidence. happiness.
I wanted my child to enjoy
the same opportunities.
That's why I sent her
to train in wrestling.
But when I think about it now…
Whether I did the right thing or not…
I'm not sure!
Parents can guide children
only up to the age of 14 or 15.
After 14 or 15.
children start making their own choices.
Until then. it's enough to teach them
the difference between right and wrong.
As parents that's our duty.
- Good morning!
Why isn't Mathi coming to school?
Teacher. she's not herself. lately.
So. she refuses to come to school.
- Mom. do you like this serial?
- People!
He did not send Mathi to school
for 4 days.
Matter needs attention.
If you don't question him
he'll destroy her life. too.
Listen. the only way to get our
child back is through legal means.
I spoke to the lawyer. already.
Let's end this circus.
Hey. shut up!
It's not even a month
since they got separated.
And you want to consult a lawyer.
Let's meet him and discuss further.
Are you going to question him
why he slapped Keerthi?
We must question him!
In the past 6 years
he has never slapped her.
If he slapped her now
there must be a reason.
So. if there's a reason you'd slap her.
That's not what I meant.
The way she's upset for hitting her child
similarly. son-in-law
must be upset for hitting her.
Let's all go together
and discuss this matter further.
Why are you being stubborn?
Please get in the car.
Do you really think they're upset
because I'm not with them?
How would they not?
The way this situation upsets you
your child and your husband
will feel that pain twice as much.
You'd believe me only
when you see it for yourself.
Get in!
I can't believe you're paying heed to me.
One important matter.
No one should utter a word
when we get there.
- Why?
- I'll speak to him.
Start the vehicle.
She's upset all the time.
She's not smiling.
Making a child smile isn't a big deal.
Step aside!
Class Teacher.
Why aren't you coming to school?
Here you go.
You don't want it?
I don't want it.
Hello!
First. put them down.
Did you notice
who he is letting down first.
When are you going to get her off?
The way this situation upsets you
your child and your husband
will feel that pain twice as much.
You asked us not to utter word
and claimed to handle the situation.
But you're not talking now.
Didn't you see what happened?
There's nothing left to say.
Son-in-law put up show for us.
It's not what you think it is.
What do you mean?
Were you planning to use another step?
It's my fault I had faith in you.
Before you got here
we were truly sad.
I don't get it. though.
The song you were dancing to
is not meant for sad situations.
Any husband away from his wife
tends to dance with joy.
That doesn't mean
you should be dancing with such joy.
Coming here opened our eyes to the truth.
- Let's leave.
- Disgusting.
What are you waiting for?
Next is legal route.
Let's go!
Keerthi…
Keerthi!
I'm doomed!
Look at this. Uncle.
She has sent me a divorce notice.
Why would she go this far?
You're handing it to him
as if he knows English!
I had to read it out to you.
Veera. if we go to court.
they will rule that the daughter
must live with her mother.
That's why they sent you
the divorce notice.
That's not fair.
So. when you withdraw cash from an ATM.
does it belong to the machine
or the person who withdrew it?
Gosh!
Brother. don't talk nonsense
in court like you do here.
The judge will get you arrested.
Veera. there's no point in getting angry.
The court demands evidence.
Only if you produce
the Ayurvedic doctor in court
can you prove your innocence.
I'm not sure where he's hiding.
He's not opening his clinic either.
What the hell?
We could've easily won.
- It's okay. Coach.
- We'll make it up next time.
Doctor. over here!
You can reopen the clinic now.
He won't come looking for you.
He'll be running back and forth
between court and home.
Doctor. why is your face swollen?
He somehow sought me out from hiding.
Only if you present
the Ayurveda Doctor in the court
can you prove yourself innocent.
It's 3.500 rupees for the medicine.
You met them at the temple. is it?
Only after visiting
other rituals would follow.
Let me know how you got lucky.
I've been trying for 15 years.
Bless me. God!
Hey. please don't harm me.
The Coach is the
cause of all the problems.
The Coach?
I ought to!
I blindly trusted you.
Wrestling is a sport
that you play face to face.
You're not fit to be
called a sportsperson.
You're right!
I shouldn't be in the field of sports.
Only your wife deserves to be in sports.
Only she plays. wins medals.
and gets promotions.
But I should be just sitting ducks.
Neither they respect me at the office.
Nor do they respect me at the Academy.
In fact.
I don't get respect even at my home.
The other day. she said.
"My husband is the reason for my success."
Just because you cook three meals a day
doesn't mean you're the reason
for her success.
That's not what she meant.
I'm the Coach!
Giving me some credit
wouldn't make her any less.
- That's why…
- Stop!
I wanted to defeat her
in wrestling this time.
Just defeating her won't be enough.
So. I decided to drive her
out of the field altogether.
Now her career has been destroyed.
Keerthi! Keerthi!
Keerthi!
Do you know who's behind all our problems?
It's the Coach. right?
How did you know?
The Coach told himself.
Keerthi. look at what your husband
has done to me.
He's threatening
me into telling you
that I influenced him
to give you the meds.
I refused to say it. and I got beaten up.
He's lying!
I'm going to wait and see what else
you would do to hide your mistakes.
- Keerthi...
- You beat him up mercilessly.
Trust me. Keerthi. He's lying!
- I swear he asked me to give you the meds.
- Don't say anything.
Please don't say anything.
- Trust me. Keerthi.
- I trusted you enough.
If you have anything to say.
say it in court.
I don't wish to talk to you anymore.
Keerthi! Keerthi!
You believe in his words.
But you're refusing to believe me.
Being uneducated.
I foolishly trusted everything he told me.
Aren't you educated?
But you're a bigger fool than me.
Going to court won't fix our problems.
I don't know
how else to make you understand.
Dad. Mom's out there.
- Sir. Judge Vishwanathan is on leave.
- Who is replacing him?
Raja Rajeshwari.
Oh. no. not her!
PRINCIPAL DISTRICT JUDGE
COIMBATORE.
It's our bad luck she's the judge today.
What happened. sir?
That Judge won't let the lawyers argue.
She'll speak for herself.
whatever the lawyer has to say.
If she questions you be straight forward
and ask for divorce.
She's a very tricky person.
Lately. in our country. divorce cases are
on the rise more than theft and murder.
Not sure where it's headed.
Proceed!
HMOP 1520/2026 Veera - Keerthi.
Your Honor. my client...
Why should there be a 3rd party
between a husband and wife.
Didn't they get married?
- Madam. I'm a lawyer.
- Even lawyer shouldn't interfere.
Sit down!
Please proceed. dear.
- What do you want?
- I want my daughter.
I want my father.
I want my wife.
Then what am I doing here?
What are client's demand?
That's what I was trying to
tell you earlier.
Why wouldn't you tell now?
Sure. My Lord!
My client's husband has been working
as a house husband for the past 7 years.
They had their differences.
And the reason was a disagreement
over how to raise the child.
Envious of my client's achievements
in wrestling.
Veera. a house husband.
plotted repeatedly to ensure her defeat.
So. I request that he be
sentenced to death. Your Honor.
Enough! I'm not surprised
because you brought this lawyer to us.
- What's happening. Sattam?
- Hey!
Sorry. Your Honor. I said it in a flow.
Pegs himself to be Tiger Dayanidhi.
Sit down. damn it!
If you didn't like to
remain a house husband.
why didn't you tell your wife?
Why did you spoil her life?
- Your Honor. my client...
- Don't you see I'm talking to him?
Stop interfering! Sit down!
Go ahead!
The respect I received
when I was lurking like a loafer
I did not receive it
when I became a house husband.
That being said. even my uncle
has not spoken to me for years now.
A man should do household chores.
And sharing other work with your wife
is what society preaches.
But mock the men who do household chores.
It's because we have never
respected a housewife.
We keep pointing out that
they stay at home idle. doing nothing.
People go out to do a job.
But for the ones who stay home.
they work from dawn till dusk.
They don't have holidays
or weekends to relax and enjoy.
All days are the same to them.
TRUTH ALONE TRIUMPHS
If a man is achieving in his career.
then his wife is behind his success.
Many don't realize it.
There's a woman behind
every man's success.
Imagine if there's a man behind
a woman's success
and it's the husband.
That woman would be
the happiest in the world.
I wish to be that man in Keerthi's life.
You spoke a lot.
Then. why did you poison her food?
I did not poison her. It was medicine.
That's what I meant.
Why did you do it?
May I ask you one question. Madam?
- Proceed!
- Madam. what is toughest job in the world?
Why don't you answer it yourself?
- It's being a husband.
- What?
I'm telling the truth. Madam.
Being a husband is tough job
than being a Judge.
You had to graduate to become a Judge.
Because there books to learn about law.
So. you know what to do and when.
But there is no study material or degree
that teaches you how to be a husband.
There's no specific book available
that teaches you to be one.
We're clueless in what to do and when.
Day in and day out.
we get yelled at by our wives.
I've made plenty of mistakes
in my role as a husband.
I am not denying it.
But I'm slowly rectifying it
one after another.
Please give me some time.
Not divorce me.
Do you think any husband would
go to such lengths to plead as he did?
Find a way to work out your differences.
Ma'am he ruined everything.
Just speaking modestly
won't make him a good man.
Please ask them to play this.
What is this?
- Uncle. why are you recording?
- For proof!
Who's that woman?
She's my daughter's Class Teacher.
While going to pick up our daughter.
he picked up the teacher as well.
What's the guarantee
that she won't be my daughter's stepmom?
Then. my daughter would
have to endure stepmom tortures.
I don't want that for my daughter.
Please give me a divorce.
Mister. you did everything possible
but churning our dialogues
about supporting your wife.
Bloody rascal!
- It's not what it looks like...
- Shut up!
Please come here.
Come here!
Your husband has put you through a lot.
Do you want him to be happy
or be worried all his life?
He should be worried all his life.
Then don't divorce him.
What if he resumes dancing
with the teacher after the divorce?
Keep him with you.
Only then will he be on his toes
all the time.
I'm speaking out of experience.
I don't get what you're saying.
My husband did the same thing
as your husband did.
Do you see the typist sitting out there?
- He had an affair with her.
- Oh. no!
I told him to stay home
and not come to the court.
I could've chased him out of the house.
But I didn't do it.
Instead. keep him beside you
and make his life hell.
I don't think so. Ma'am.
Let him dance with whomever he wants to.
I don't care a damn about it.
Please give me a divorce right away
and give my daughter back.
- Please!
- What do you think of yourself?
You're repeating like a broken record.
You want me.
but you don't want Dad. is it?
Dear. you must not yell inside the court.
If you run your court properly.
why would I be screaming?
Mathi!
You're asking only what they both want.
I'm their daughter.
Why aren't you asking me?
You have a point. dear.
Fine.
Now. tell me.
With whom do you like to live
after your parents get divorced?
Husband and wife can divorce each other.
That's their wish.
But my parents must not divorce.
That's my wish!
The child's approval
is very important in this case.
I'm giving you both some time.
The next hearing will be after 3 months.
Until then. I order you both
to attend family counseling.
This is my decree!
And my decree is law!
Ma'am. this is not a kingdom?
To churn out punchlines.
I cannot wait for three months.
Please let me take my daughter home.
How dare you bark orders at me?
Who's the judge here. you or me?
I can't pass a verdict
at your convenience.
Only now has this dispute
been brought before the court.
It's not a mutual divorce. either.
Until you are divorced. who would have
the custody of your daughter
is something
the family must discuss and decide.
My head is spinning
after listening to you people speak.
I'm stepping out to have a cup of tea.
And when I return.
I'll tell you when the next hearing is.
Velu. bring the flask to my chamber.
Hey. I'm talking to you.
Come with me.
- Yes. Madam!
- Go.
Hey. keep moving.
Stop being lazy.
How dare you yell at the Judge?
Can't you maintain discipline?
Who taught you this behavior?
We come from a brave bloodline.
Tell her that we are not afraid
of the court or the Judge.
Please keep this nonsense to yourself.
Don't influence my daughter.
What do you mean?
She's our blood.
I hate these words. blood and legacy.
Just because you don't like it
we can't do anything about it.
I don't care. Bro!
Why are you
running your mouth unnecessarily?
- What?
- Have you forgotten the slap
that you got for speaking nonsense?
Would you like another slap from her?
My nephew returned that slap
with interest that very moment.
Just because you're stronger
doesn't mean you beat up everyone.
If she's a wrestler.
my nephew is a wrestler too.
- Oh. God!
- Got it?
Bro. we're having
a serious discussion here.
But you're joking in court
by calling him a wrestler.
Joking?
My nephew would've kicked her
like a football in the Palakkad match.
She escaped because she got pregnant.
Who was saved on that day.
- your nephew or me?
- It's you!
The people saw my nephew's match.
Do you even know who he won against?
Coach! A male Coach!
Compared to the Coach.
you're an ordinary player.
That too. you're a women player.
- Are you going to shut up or not?
- Uncle!
Please stop talking unnecessarily.
Why did we come to court?
She's been challenging.
yet you're asking me to back down.
Indeed. I'm a woman player.
But I'm ready to fight again.
Why don't you check
if your male player is ready?
Now you're talking. my girl.
- Keerthi. what's this nonsense?
- What did I do?
I'll speak now!
My father is ready to fight you.
Hey. sweetie. please stay quiet.
Why are you dragging me into this?
We can beat her only
if we play her game.
Please don't say anything
for a while and stand out there.
Go! Go and stand out there.
I'm not blowing up this problem.
I don't know what you have in mind.
Go!
- It'll be humiliating for us.
- How do we get our child back?
My father did not train for 15 years
to become a wrestler.
He only trained for 15 days.
Yet he won't the match.
Your father won once in his lifetime.
That's called luck not talent.
My father took part in only one match.
Yet he won that match.
- Hey. Baby...
- Hey!
We're discussing about wrestling.
You have nothing to do with it.
Hey. you're going overboard.
Apologize to him.
Why should I apologize to him?
What does he know about wrestling?
Hey. fake candy.
All these years. you fooled people
by calling yourself a wrestler.
But a young kid smeared you
with dung and humiliated you.
Had it been me.
I would have killed myself.
You claim
that my client won by luck. right?
We'll prove it wrong.
When is the match?
- Sattam!
- We'll have it tomorrow.
- But one condition.
- What's the condition?
If he wins the match…
Mathi can live with him.
But if I win…
You should send Mathi with me.
- That's not right. Pick something else.
- Now. I challenge you to talk.
What? Are you scared?
My father is ready for the competition.
But there's a change in the condition.
What change?
If you win. I'll come with you.
Okay!
But if my father wins.
you should come with us.
Sweetie. stop talking nonsense.
I don't want a competition.
Let her go with her.
I don't have any qualms about it.
I don't want your charity.
I'll win in the competition
and then take her.
You. people. fix the venue.
We'll conduct at the Temple ground.
Uncle. why are you doing this?
If you insist let's conduct it
inside our house.
Not at a ground.
Oh. he is avoid the humiliation
in front of the people.
Uncle. this is a family matter.
It won't look good
if we fight in public.
Didn't you fight your wife
in front of people before?
- What happened now?
- How dare you?
You're disrespecting him.
You better speak with respect.
This is how I speak.
Are you trying to cheat
by holding the match inside the house?
The match will take place
at the ground.
No one can change it...
- Sattam. please make them understand.
- Be respectful!
- Ask him to keep quiet.
- Please be quiet.
Uncle. please!
Please hear me out.
- Please don't yell inside the court.
- We'll talk it out.
Everyone. please calm down.
- Lawyer. tell them to keep quiet.
- He is going on and on!
- How can I keep quiet?
- Order! Order! Order!
Do you think you're in a court
or a market?
What did I instruct you people to do?
Did you discuss and come to a decision?
Who's taking the kid?
We're not going to discuss
to make a decision. Ma'am.
Instead. we're going to
play against each other.
Play against each other. you say?
- What game?
- Wrestling!
Whoever wins can get the child's custody.
Never before have I passed
such an unusual verdict.
You should officiate this competition.
They will cheat us.
There's no space for such a decision.
You may conduct the competition.
I'll come there as an audience.
I have a long standing wish
to watch a wrestling match live.
And if the match is between
a husband and a wife
quite exciting!
I'm also excited. Madam.
Case dismissed!
THE HUSBAND OR THE WIFE?
NOT JUST IN INDIAN HISTORY!
THIS IS A FIRST IN WORLD HISTORY!
OPEN WRESTLING MATCH
BETWEEN HUSBAND AND WIFE
Why are you charging 100 bucks
to watch a husband and wife fight?
How's this fair?
It's 100 bucks when
you buy at the counter.
If you're late by half an hour
it'll be sold in black for 500 bucks.
Scoot!
- Come on. pay up.
- Three tickets.
Give me a 140ml.
140? The ticket cost is only 100 bucks.
Lining up immediately
looking at the queue.
Oh. he mistook it for another shop.
Are you happy now?
I wanted to finish this competition
without anyone's knowledge.
You suggested temple ground and
now see the crowd it has gathered.
Sorry. Son.
We didn't expect
so many people to show up.
How did everyone come to know about it?
Sattam told his wife all about
what happened in court.
She's an admin of four
or five WhatsApp group.
She put out a broadcast message.
People won't spread the good news.
But if it's a bad news
they'll compete to spread the message.
But why are you selling tickets?
Or else we won't be able to
control the crowd.
I'm not going to take this money.
Look over there.
- Who are they?
- Cheers girls!
No game can be held without cheer girls.
as per the new Government rule.
There are a group of fans for cheer girls.
Look. the Judge is also eager
to watch the fight.
Greetings. Madam Judge.
I reckon you'll win this match.
What are you thinking about?
Your daughter has faith in you
and have placed bets.
Win this fight
and bring the family back together.
- Show me your ticket!
- Hey. it's the Judge!
I'll handle you when
you come to the court.
Oh. no. please don't Madam.
Hey. Sweetie. are you ready
to watch Mom and Dad's match?
Don't forget you're up against
a State Champion.
The same State Champion trained with me
to spar with her.
I know her all movements.
Dad. speaking about it here
is not important.
It should reflect in the ring.
Dad. please manage to win the match.
I will. dear.
Don't say you'd try your best.
So. make a promise.
And prove that my Dad is a Hero.
Please do it. Dad.
Promise! For you!
The most anticipated competition
is about to begin!
- I'm going in. Take care.
- You carry on.
Uncle. please hand me your phone.
My phone? Here you go.
- Who are you calling?
- Meenu Teacher.
- I'm inviting her to watch the match.
- Oh. no!
You're going to mess everything up.
As it is your mother is going to
knead your father to ground.
If your teacher shows up
then your father will be a minced parotta.
Cricket commentators
were once successful players.
So. to begin this match
and to render commentary…
We welcome former Punjab Wrestler.
Balbir Singh.
Please give him a warm welcome.
He's the direct successor of
Undertaker from the world of wrestling.
No one calls him
but he claims it himself.
Greetings to all!
A group is waiting to watch
if the husband would beat up the wife.
Another group is waiting to watch
if the wife would beat up the husband.
In fact. to see other families
fight with each other
all of you are here to enjoy the match.
You shouldn't be applauding
but feel ashamed.
Bring them out!
You're going to fight
with your wife. right?
Then. why are you hyping it up?
Don't bother about it.
You seem like a true bred Tamilian.
But they're calling you a Punjab wrestler.
Dinesh Karthick plays for Bengaluru.
Even Nataraj plays for Delhi.
What's wrong if I go to Punjab to wrestle?
Are you here to fight
or to interview me?
Call out your wife!
Oh! She's not even wearing a track suit.
I think she believes she can
take you down even in a saree.
Hey. I know what's running on your mind.
Why is she wearing a saree?
She's going to sprinkle you
like the dung on the wall.
Posing won't help you win the match.
Just because I was posing.
the Biharis beat me up.
stripping me down to underwear.
I'm helping you get away.
Escape on the bike.
I won't!
Fate has never spared anyone.
He won't back down. it seems.
Woman. hurry up.
Keerthi! Keerthi!
Welcome. Dear!
I think she just did push ups.
The only request I would like to
put forward to the Government is…
It's simple.
Conduct husband and wife fights…
On a stage yearly like a IPL match
they wouldn't have to go to court
and save up on lawyer's fee.
The Judge Madam
should approve this request.
He keeps yapping nonsense!
In today's 20-20 wrestling match
whoever scores 20 points first
they will be the winner of the match.
Red colour cheer girls support Keerthi.
Blue colour cheer girls support Veera.
Hey. I'm red too. Same family.
Hey. the colour on
the side of the jersey is yours.
You don't even know the basics and you're
here to fight wearing a swimming costume.
Ready. first round.
Come on. break his jaw.
Is she taking his blessings?
Like she dusted her hands.
she's about to dust off her husband…
I'm giving you the warrior princess.
Hey. you too pull up a stance.
Why are you standing idle
like you're waiting for a bus?
Huh! People!
Shout out your cheers!
Come on. cheer!
Oh. God!
Fight your wife. damn it.
Not me!
Ready!
It's a wonderful spectacle to watch.
This is what you call a great fight.
Hey. instead of fighting.
why are you giving her weird looks?
Woman. hit him so hard that
he should not stand up for his life.
Oh. God!
Since he got in the ring.
he's only been beating me.
His gaze it not a fighter's gaze.
He must fight and explain his gaze.
Woman. do a somersault.
Damn you!
Instead of fighting each other
they're throwing sand at me.
Hey. stop! First round over.
I shall go up to the stage
to continue the commentary.
- How's my game. Sattam?
- Super. Veera!
I underestimated you.
You haven't lost touch.
Second round. start!
Veera. keep it up!
That's it!
Twist his arms.
Don't spare him.
Just like you flip a parotta…
She flipped her husband in the air.
Wonderful shot!
- 4 points!
- Dad!
Hey. get up.
You're lying down as if you're chilling.
Hey. is he an old fighter?
You can't teach him.
Take him away.
She's thrashing him like washing clothes.
- Oh. no!
- Hey!
No man has ever won a battle
against his wife.
Mathi. do you think your father will win?
I'm clueless just like you. Ma'am.
Yeah. Keerthi. that's it.
That's super!
Second rounds. ends.
I pity the blue colour cheer girls.
He's not going to
give you the opportunity to dance.
Please have your food
and sleep at home.
Have it.
Damn. she exhausted her husband
by the second round.
And he's shamelessly drinking water.
I wonder if in the third round he would
drink water again
or ride in the ambulance.
Hey. stop with the yapping.
I don't need it anymore.
Hey. Veera.
I'm giving you a second chance.
Escape from here.
They're trolling you.
Next round thrash her.
Uncle. be careful. it's hurting.
Why aren't you thrashing her?
She's using a new technique.
- You can do it!
- He has started to shiver in pain.
- Don't give up. Veera.
- Come on! Come on!
He's only full of theatrics.
Either way. he's going to get beaten up.
What just happened?
He scored a point!
Hey!
How's my game now?
You just scored two points
didn't win the match yet.
She has scored 12 points.
You need 10 more to level with her.
That's like it. my boy!
Hey. Keerthi!
That was a wonderful shot!
Keerthi back to form!
Come on!
This fight is not circumstantial.
It was years of suppressed anger
that Keerthi finally let out on him.
Dad. come on. get up!
Oh. God!
Third round. ends.
Dad must win.
My father is also a
wrestler!
My father is a wrestler. just like you.
He won against a coach.
Dad must win.
Prove that you're a Hero.
Fourth round. start!
You need to score only one more point.
Finish him off!
4 points!
What happened?
What is wrong with her?
Aren't you ashamed
to score points like this?
Among husband and wife.
it doesn't matter who scores first.
Keep it coming!
Veera was weak
in all the previous rounds.
But how is he performing so well
in the last round?
Even I. a heavyweight wrestler.
don't understand it.
Dad!
19-19. equal!
Why is she stepping back?
Is Veera using a new technique?
Keerthi. come on. come on!
Ready. ready. ready!
One more point to win.
Time is running out.
Don't miss it.
That's it. Cross the line!
One more point. Cross the line.
Quit fooling around and cross the line!
He's back in the ring.
- Keerthi!
- Why did she faint?
Keerthi!
Kee... Keerthi!
Keerthi. what happened?
Keerthi!
Hey. Sattam!
Mom!
- Keerthi!
- What happened to Mom?
Mom!
- Mom!
- She was playing well.
Dear!
I suspect Veera has something
to do with it.
Was he actually playing a fair match?
Or was he resorting to tricks?
Oh. God! Don't just stand there.
Help me!
Lift her.
Let's take her to the hospital.
Wait a minute.
Let me check what's wrong.
Nothing to worry.
It's good news!
She's pregnant.
What does that mean?
You're going to have a baby brother. dear.
She's pregnant?!
Why are you anxious?
He wouldn't go to work
when they had only one child.
Now they're having another!
I think I must quit my job.
Pregnant?
Bloody sinners!
In my years of wrestling experience.
this is the first time someone has
gotten pregnant during a fight.
You two were in this together.
and you still had the audacity
to file for divorce!
Bloody rascals!
No matter how big the problem is.
my nephew solves it
by getting her pregnant.
Hey. Uncle!
Guys!
First they wrestled in bed.
then came here to wrestle in the ring.
We must learn something from this.
A quarrel between husband and wife
isn't a third person's business.
That's the moral of this story.
Everyone. get going! Leave!
Are you happy?
Two babies?
I only asked for one.
Another one is a bonus.
You promised to make me
the Mary Kom of sports.
Instead. you gave me three kids
and turned me into a homemaker Mary Kom.
I won't go back on my word.
I won't rest until I make you
the Mary Kom of sports.
I swear on my three children.
Since you're pregnant.
I didn't want to hide the truth from you.
The coach devised a plan to defeat you.
Today. I may have won.
But this victory belongs to you.
I was in love with a guy for four years.
He said. "I don't like you wearing
this costume and playing this game."
"It makes me uncomfortable
when other men look at you."
He said. "Please quit wrestling
after we get married."
I told him. "I don't mind leaving you.
but I can't quit wrestling."
He was well-educated.
but his thinking was flawed.
But your husband is uneducated.
Even after you gave birth.
he wanted you to succeed in wrestling.
Don't miss this opportunity.
Wow!
Come on. Keerthi!
- Cheer for Mom.
- Mom!
Hey. Mom is looking at you guys.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today